Finding Aid for the Lawrence Clark Powell Papers LSC.0229
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Manuscripts Of Articles And Lectures, ca. 1950-1971
  - Boxes 83-104
    - Sou- Ten
      - Strictly Local. LCP State Colleges Series, April 22, 1965. (Box 101, Folder 15)
      - Student Handbook Welcome, 1960. (Box 101, Folder 16)
      - Sullivan, Maude Durlin; Pioneer Southwest Library Powell, L.C. foreword to, 1872-1944 Spring 1962. (Box 101, Folder 17)
      - Summerhayes, Winter Days with (or Vanished Arizona & Arizona Today) Arizona Highways, January 1961. (Box 101, Folder 18)
      - Summer Miscellany--California Librarian, (Midsummer Miscellany)., September 1952 (Box 101, Folder 19)
      - Summing Up. CLA, Southern District, April 16, 1966. (Box 101, Folder 20)
      - Talismans for the Traveler. In Southwest Review. (Box 101, Folder 21)
      - Teaching with Books: A Study of College Libraries, by Branscomb. Review by LCP in Library Journal. (Box 101, Folder 22)
      - Ten Books -- For Page Gilman, 1954. (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - TEX - THR
      - Texas, University of. (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - This Dry and Wrinkled Land. Tucson, Arizona State Library Association, April 11, 1953. (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Thomas C. Lancey, Chronicler of '46. In Pacific Historical Review, February 1947. (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Thompson Book, foreword. (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Those Beautiful Back Roads. (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - Thoughts on professionalism. Institute on the Personnel Needs of Public and Special Libraries -- San Francisco University. (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - Three H's, printing of 1996 Zabreb talk., June 1971 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - Three L's, Speech to American Hist... UCLA (Browning Society version). (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - Three L's, Conference of California Association of School Librarian., Friday March 5, 1965. (Box 102, Folder 9)
      - Three L's, Browning Society, San Francisco, (new mms.)., February 28, 1964. (Box 102, Folder 10)
      - Three L's, Friends and Patrons of the Santa Ana Public Library., April 16, 1964. (Box 102, Folder 11)
      - Three L's, The Grolier Club, New York, January 23, 1964. (Box 102, Folder 12)
      - Three L's Mount Shasta District CLA meeting, Oroville, May 8, 1965. (Box 102, Folder 13)
      - Three L's, PACAF Library Workshop. (Box 102, Folder 14)
      - Three L's, University Affiliates, W.A. Clark Memorial Library, April 13, 1964. (Box 102, Folder 15)
      - Three L's,Watkins House Associates, Riverside, March 24, 1965. (Box 102, Folder 16)
      - Three Loves Have I --Randolph G. Adals Memorial Lecture, Ann Arbor, Michigan, October 1953. (Box 102, Folder 17)
      - Three O'Clock Appointment -- Hoja Volante, January, 1955. (Box 102, Folder 18)
      - Three Who Fed Me. New Haven, April 18, 1968. (Box 102, Folder 19)
      - Through the Burning Glass. (Box 102, Folder 20)
        (Delivered on several occasions. See blue card)
    - THR - V
      - Through the Burning Glass. (Box 103, Folder 1)
        Miscellaneous correspondence/Typescripts.
      - The Time, the Place, and the Book. Introduction to Vaquero of the Brush Country by J. Frank Dobie. (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - The Time, the Place and the Poem. Browning Society. San Francisco, January 9, 1959. (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - Time to Join. In UCLA Librarian, January 8, 1960. (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Time to Read -- Foreword for Harry Levinson, January 1954. (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Tokyo Workshop - Fifth Airforce. (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - To Newbury to Buy an Old Book -- Van Patten Festschrift, July 1952. (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - To Touch or Not to Touch. In ALA Bulletin, 1958. (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Trailer Library. A Reading list offered by LCP in Westways., May 1961. (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - Trailing Books - LCP Los Angeles Times, March 15, 1955. (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - Transcontinental -- California Librarian, June 1952. (Box 103, Folder 11)
      - Traven, B. Miller book. LCP evaluation, February 1967. (Box 103, Folder 12)
      - Trouble with Titles. In Los Angeles Times, November 26, 1956. (Box 103, Folder 13)
      - Turner Book foreword, 1972. (Box 103, Folder 14)
      - Twenty-Five Good Books About Mexico. (Box 103, Folder 15)
      - Two Small Books -- Hoja Volante, !ay, 1952. (Box 103, Folder 16)
      - Two Years Before the Mast. (Review of by LCP ) Southern California Quarterly., January 1965 (Box 103, Folder 17)
      - Tycoons' Barbecue. Pacific Palisades' Superior Library, June 30, 1960. (Box 103, Folder 18)
      - Unfinished Manuscripts. (Box 103, Folder 19)
      - UNESCO Conference -- Nice, France, April 10, 1953. (Box 103, Folder 20)
      - UCLA Library Schools Alumni Association (no title), 1961. (Box 103, Folder 21)
      - University of Arizona Foundation Anything Goes, April 12, 1971. (Box 103, Folder 22)
      - UCLA School of Library Service. School Library Association of Southern California Bulletin. (Box 103, Folder 23)
      - University of California, Riverside (no title) Campus Club Officers' Spring Tea, May 13, 1961. (Box 103, Folder 24)
      - Unlikely Trio. In Wesleyan, April 17, 1968. (Box 103, Folder 25)
      - USC Library School Alumni ()., May 10, 1947 (Box 103, Folder 26)
      - Up Near the Source. (Box 103, Folder 27)
        (2 occasions, see blue card)
      - Use of Special Materials in Historical Research and Teaching -- History Institute, UC Extension, November 5, 1949. (Box 103, Folder 28)
      - Van Patten, Nathan. Libri., May 1956. (Box 103, Folder 29)
      - Vroman's (no title) annual meet the authors luncheon, March 17, 1959. (Box 103, Folder 30)
      - Vroman's of Pasadena --, 1953. (Box 103, Folder 31)
    - W - Z
      - Wagner, Henry R. Talk given at Wagner Memorial Banquet, California Historical Society. San Francisco, September 25, 1964. (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Wagner, Henry R. (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - War Books. Read to UCLA Library Staff, by LCP., May 11, 1943 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Way it Sounds to Me -- Music Library Association,; San Francisco Browning Society, and others., June 24, 1953 January 21, 1954 (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Way it Sounds to Me. In Southwest Review and Best Articles and Stories. (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Way of Life. Trumbull Lecture. Yale University, January 25, 1960. (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Wector memorial. (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Welcome (for Institute for Library Administration, by LCP)., August 7, 1957 (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - Welcome Address -- Institute on Library Work for Children, Extension, June 1953. (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - Welcome Address. Medical Library Association. UCLA, June 20, 1956. (Box 104, Folder 10)
      - We Moderns -- Wilson Library Bulletin, November 1945. (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - We Moved to the Malibu. In Los Angeles Times, August 22, 1955. (Box 104, Folder 12)
      - Weber, F.J. Bibliography of Los Angeles, August 1970. (Box 104, Folder 13)
      - Welcome to an Exciting Profession - S.L.S., August 18, 1967. (Box 104, Folder 14)
      - Wesleyan University. Center for Advanced Studies. (Box 104, Folder 15)
      - Westlake School for Girls - speech, no title, January 8, 1964. (Box 104, Folder 16)
      - West Southeast -- Southeastern Libraries, January 1955. (Box 104, Folder 17)
      - Westways (Correspondence). (Box 104, Folder 18)
      - What's Wrong with Librarians? Occasional Papers (no.9), 1959. (Box 104, Folder 19)
      - Wilson Library Bull, 1943. (Box 104, Folder 20)
      - Whittier College Faculty Dinner, April 17, 1944. (Box 104, Folder 21)
      - With Books in my Baggage; or, A Bookman Traveler in Arizona. In Arizona Highways. (Box 104, Folder 22)
      - Within These Walls a Dreal Come True. Affiliates, UCLA, November 14, 1955. (Box 104, Folder 23)
      - Writers of the Southwest. Los Angeles City College; Westerner, May 27, 1955 May 19, 1955. (Box 104, Folder 24)
      - Homage to W.B. Yeats. Browning Society, February 26, 1965. (Box 104, Folder 25)
      - Yelland (Edna) Letter, honoring her retirement from California Librarian., September 1963 (Box 104, Folder 26)
      - You, John Milton. Address to University of Oklahoma, Norman, January 4, 1966. (Box 104, Folder 27)
      - Zagreb Talk, November 1966. (Box 104, Folder 28)
      - Zamorano Roxburghe ()., September 11, 1954 (Box 104, Folder 29)
      - Z is for Zurich. In Herald-Examiner, January 12, 1964. (Box 104, Folder 30)
      - Zeitlin - 65th, 1967. (Box 104, Folder 31)
- Additions, 1975-
  - LCP's copy of Hoja Volante; books by LCP. (Box 105)
  - LCP's Writings
    - Books, and articles in Westways magazine. (Box 106)
    - Miscellaneous to, 1975. (Box 107)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-January 1983. (Box 108)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence files, including Regrets.. (Box 109)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence files; commemorative plaque and T-shirt featuring LCP. (Box 110)
  - Correspondence files transfered by letter of, September 25, 1978. (Box 111)
  - Files relating to positions held by LCP. (Box 112)
  - Card indexes to publications,, and to occasions on which speeches were given in the, ca. 1950's-1960's 1960's. (Box 113)
  - LCP's writings: Miscellaneous, February 1983-1987. (Box 114, Box 115)
  - Interview with Lawrence Clark Powell, June 1987.; (3 videotapes and typed transcription) (Box 116)
- Postcards
  Note: where brackets appear around page (p.) or leaf (l.) numbers in the text, this indicates that the number represents the total of a series of unnumbered pages or leaves.
  - Postcards. (Box 117)
  - Postcards - Oversize. (Box 118)
  - Santa Cruz Library talk, March 20, 1977. (Box 118)
  - Archives talk - UCLA, 1972. (Box 118)
  - Lake talk., 31 May 1975. (Box 118)
  - Coulter, Edith M. (Box 118)
  - Irvine talk., June 1976. (Box 118)
  - Saul Marks. (Box 118)
  - Los Angeles Times piece on LCP, March 1975. (Box 118)
  - California Historical Society. Sacramento, March 3, 1973. (Box 118)
  - View from across the river. UCLA, November 12, 1975. (Box 118)
  - UCLA talk, May 6, 1973. (Box 118)
  - Friends of Occidental College. Pasadena, March 19, 1974. (Box 118)
  - W.W. Robinson - LCP eulogy, 1972. (Box 118)
  - Postcards
    - Alabama - Delaware. (Box 121)
    - Florida - Maryland. (Box 122)
    - Massachusetts - Michigan. (Box 123)
    - Minnesota - North Dakota. (Box 124)
    - Ohio - Washington State. (Box 125)
      (missing May 1990)
    - Washington D.C. - end (also, Foreign). (Box 126)
- LCP bibliography. (Box 119)
- LCP name index. (Box 120)
- Printed material. (Box 127)
- Photographs of LCP exhibit in Powell Library, 1966. (Box 128)
- Looking back and remembering. An autobiographical sketch by Gertrude Eliza Clark Powell. With a prologue and epilogue by LCP. Tucson: Privately printed, 1987.; (Typescript) (Box 128)
- An orange grove boyhood. by LCP. Santa Barbara: Capra Press, 1988. (Box 128)
- Correspondence with Tony Long, Harriet Harris, Harriet Barkhurt, et al. Subsequent to Haniel's death. (Box 128)
- The wilderness still lingers. The Southwestern landscape in literature. A two-part audio program., (1 cassette tape) (Box 128)
  Presented by the Arizona Humanities Council and the Tucson Public Library's Writers of the purple sage project. Includes: I'm wondering what Powell would say... - an interview with LCP.
- Return to the heartland. Reminiscences of Texas books and book people. by LCP. DeGoyler Library Keepsake no.2. Dallas, 1987. (Box 128)
- The Mustangs. by J. Frank Dobie. Boston: Little, Brown & Company, 1952. (Box 129)
  Note from Dobie to LCP written on leaf following front endpaper, dated Christmas 1957.
- Guide to the life and literature of the Southwest. by J. Frank Dobie. Dallas: SMU Press, 1952.; (Hard covers) (Box 129)
  Inscrition by Dobie to LCP dated November 29-30, 1954 on front endpaper.
- Guide to the life and literature of the Southwest. by J. Frank Dobie. Dallas: SMU Press, 1952.; (Paper covers) (Box 129)
  Inscription by Dobie to LCP dated May 22 1954, on front endpaper.
- J. Frank Dobie. Clippings, photographs and ephemera. (Box 129)
- Certificate of membership in Phi Gamma Delta. (Box 130)
- Recording of broadcast with Monitor program., 1960; (33 1/3 rpm. LP microgroove record) (Box 130)
- Dedication. The Hunt Library and The Rachel McMasters Miller Hunt Botanical Library. Carnegie Institute of Technology, October 10, 1961. (Box 130)
- Holman, William R. Library Publications. San Francisco, Roger Beacham, (Forward by LCP)., 1965. (Box 130)
- West Malibu. Community Council scrapbook, 1955-1956. (Box 130)
- 2 scrapbooks. LCP, 1959-1962 & 1962-1967. (Box 131)
- Scrapbook, 1959-1960. (Box 132)
  A Passion for Books and Books in my baggage.
- In honor of Henry Miller's 80th. birthday, January 9, 1972.; (1 reel audio tape. 7.5 p.s. unedited dub) (Box 132)
  LCP address at UCLA, Dickson Art Center.
  Introduction of LCP by Lawrence Durrell.
- Diplome de Docteur de l'Universite, (Diploma from Dijon University)., 29 October, 1932 (Box 133)
- Fellow of the California Historical Society certificate, March 3, 1973. (Box 133)
- 2 City of Los Angeles Commendations, April 19, 1971. (Box 133)
- Card Index to LCP's Correspondence
  - A - L. (Box 134)
  - M - Z. (Box 135)
- Publications by Powell and others. (Box 136)
  Including Peggy Pond Church and Haniel Long.
  Also, snapshot of May Sarton.
- ** Post Publication Material
  - Responses to Fay, 1993-1994. (Box 228, Folder 3-4)
  - Southwest: Three Definitions, 1990. (Box 229, Folder 9)
    Letters received, clippings.
  - Eucalyptus Fair, 1992. (Box 229, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, typescript of introduction, clippings.
  - Eucalyptus Fair, 1992-1994. (Box 230, Folder 3)
    Responses.
  - Evening Redness, 1991-1992. (Box 230, Folder 6)
    Responses received.
  - Responses to various books, 1990-1994. (Box 230, Folder 7)
  - Mysterious Transformation, 1993-1994. (Box 230, Folder 11)
  - Islands of Books, 1990-1991. (Box 231, Folder 4)
    Clippings, correspondence, typescript of new introduction.
  - Remembering Henry Miller, 1980-1991. (Box 232, Folder 5)
    Letters received, copies of diary entries, notes, drafts.
  - Arizona: A History, 1989-1992. (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - Reviews, Proofs, Letters Received, Preface to New Edition
  - Land of Fiction. Letters received, 1991. (Box 233, Folder 3)
- ** Publication Material
  - Fay, 1993. (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Islandia memorabilia and copies of articles by LCP, 1957-1988. (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Jane Apostol foreword, 1993-1994. (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Mercurius Revivius, 1993-1995. (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - Southwest: Three Definitions, 1990. (Box 229, Folder 10)
    Printers' proofs, letters received, typescript of introduction with holograph corrections.
  - Eucalyptus Fair, 1943-1990. (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - Chronology of writing, clippings, letters received.
  - Land of Fact., 1992. (Box 233, Folder 4)
    Draft typescript, letters received.
  - Letters from the Orange Empire, 1986-1990. (Box 233, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, clippings, typescript drafts of afterword.
  - Interlinear to Cabeza de Vaca, 1936. (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Letters from the Orange Empire, 1990. (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Southwest: Three Definitions, 1990. (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - Malinche (Dona Marina), 1939. (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Poems [by Haniel Long], 1920. (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - Selected Poems by Peggy Pond, 1930-1982 1982. (Box 235, Folder 6)
    Church. Sound recording.
  - William Holman broadside. (Box 236, Folder 1)
- ** Memorabilia
  - Mozart doodle for Larry Powell by Guy Endore, 1966. (Box 228, Folder 5)
- ** Organizations
  - Tucson Botanical Gardens
    - Letters received, clippings, 1990-1995. (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - ** Tucson Public Library
    - Tucson Public Library. (Box 228, Folder 9)
      Letters received, clippings, promotional materials, essay for fundraising purposes.
  - ** UCLA / Graduate School of Library and Information Science
    - Correspondence and clips, 1989-1993. (Box 229, Folder 7)
      re the re-organization of the school.
  - ** DeGolyer Library / Southwest Review
    - Letters received, 1990-1994. (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - ** California Library Association
    - Clippings, letters received, copy of speech given, 1991-1994. (Box 230, Folder 14)
  - ** UCLA Library School
    - Clippings, letters received, 1979-1993. (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - ** UCLA
    - Clippings, 1975-1993. (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - ** Historical Society of Southern California
    - Letters received, clippings, 1988- 1993. (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - ** Lorson's Books and Prints
    - Letters received re Some Writing about Los Angeles, 1992-1993. (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - ** Marlborough School
    - Letters received, 1987-1992. (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - ** Zamorano Club
    - Letters received, programs, 1982-1993. (Box 233, Folder 8)
- ** Authors
  - Henry Miller. Clippings, letters received, 1970-1995. (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - Alan Thomas and Lawrence Durrell. Letters received, clippings, 1977-1995. (Box 228, Folder 8)
  - Peggy Pond Church and Shelley Armitage, 1986-1993. (Box 229, Folder 5)
    CLOSED filed in Vault in Box 238.
  - Letters received, Clips
  - Richard Dillon. Letters received, 1993-1995. (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - M.H. Salmon, 1993. (Box 229, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence
  - Henry Miller. Clippings, catalog of Henry Miller at UCLA, by Dan Luckenbill, 1991-1993. (Box 230, Folder 9)
  - Henry Miller, 1971-1972. (Box 232, Folder 1)
    Typescript of speech by LCP for Miller's 80th birthday, photograph, clip.
    Original Henry Miller letters.
  - Henry Miller. Letters received, clippings, memorabilia, 1943-1978. (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Henry Miller. 80th Birthday Celebration at UCLA, 1971-1985. (Box 232, Folder 3)
    Clippings, letters received, holograph and typescript drafts of speech.
  - Henry Miller. Letters received, clippings, 1973-1990. (Box 232, Folder 4)
    Original letters from Emil White.
  - Haniel Long, 1935-1986. (Box 232, Folder 6)
    Correspondence (with Tony, Alice and Haniel Long), clippings.
  - Georges Connes. (Box 232, Folder 7)
    Photocopy of typescript and typescript of L'autre Epreuve.
  - ** Henry Miller
    - Big Sur: The Way it Was, 1995.; (Video cassette recording) (Box 234, Folder 1)
- ** Friends/Friendships
  - Jake Zeitlin. Clippings, letters received, eulogy, 1974-1992. (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Roger Larson Library, 1994-1995. (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - Letters Received, Clippings, Publicity Materials About Sale
  - Letters received. A - S, 1986-1994. (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - Roger Larson. Letters received, 1991-1993. (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - Letters received. Last names beginning with D, 1991-1995. (Box 234, Folder 3)
    Richard Dillon, Ernest Dawson.
  - Letters received. Last names beginning with B, 1988-1995. (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - Letters received. Last names beginning with C, 1990-1995. (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - Letters received, 1962-1996. (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - Responses to Various Books
  - Marcel Aurousseau and J.K. Wright. Letters received, 1968-1978. (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Betty Fielden, 1991. (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Betty Fielden, 1991-1992. (Box 237, Folder 2)
    Closed. Filed in URL vault.
  - Letters to Betty Fielden from LCP, to Anne and David Fielden from Betty Fielden, 1992-1993. (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Letters to Betty Fielden, 1993. (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - 4 broadsides for the friends ca. of LCP., 1935 (Box 244, Folder 1)
- ** Pre-Publication Material
  - Eucalyptus Fair, 1992-1994. (Box 229, Folder 12)
  - Printing Costs and Invoices
  - Mysterious Transformation, 1993. (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Notes, Printing Invoices
  - Eucalyptus Fair. Notes on journal entries, 1992. (Box 230, Folder 5)
- ** Items Collected
  - The Book Collector, Spring 1994. (Box 229, Folder 13)
- ** Printers and Publishers
  - Vance Gerry. Letters received, 1988-1992. (Box 230, Folder 8)
- ** Family
  - Carolyn Barclay. Letters received, 1988-1993. (Box 230, Folder 10)
  - Norman and Armena Powell and children. Letters received, 1990-1994. (Box 233, Folder 9)
  - Lindy, Carlotta and Mario Pagone. Letters received, 1991-1995. (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Norman and Armena Powell. Letters received, 1994-1995. (Box 234, Folder 8)
  - Award from The United States Food Administration to G.H. Powell. Signed Herbert Hoover. (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - California Cultivator with picture of G.H. Powell on front cover, 1912. (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Letters received from Wilkie Powell, 1993-1994. (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence re Kevin Powell, 1981-1986. (Box 238, Folder 1)
    CLOSED. Filed in URL vault.
  - Letters from Wilkie Powell, 1995-1996. (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - Letters received from Wilkie Powell, 1994-1995. (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - Manuscripts by Wilkie Powell, 1992-1993. (Box 238, Folder 4)
- ** Librarians
  - Doyce Nunis. (Box 230, Folder 12)
    Holograph of essay / talk.
  - Wilbur Jordan Smith, 1992. (Box 230, Folder 13)
  - Eulogy by LCP, Clippings
  - James D. Hart. Clippings, letters received, 1978-1991. (Box 231, Folder 1)
- ** Biography
  - Interview by Dr. Wayne Wiegand, 1980. (Box 233, Folder 11)
- ** Photographs
  - Contact sheets of LCP head shots, 1970. (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Marengo Avenue School [Pasadena]. With holograph by LCP. (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Negatives for head shots, 1970. (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - ** Family Photo Albums
    - Middletown, Connecticut, v.d.
      - 1968. (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - 1971. (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - 1968. (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - 1968. (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - Tucson, Arizona home and garden, 1971-1972. (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - From drive West from Boston. St. Louis, Rio Grande, San Juan, Pecos, Taos, 1968. (Box 239, Folder 6)
    - Catalina, Arizona townhouse views, 1973. (Box 239, Folder 7)
    - Including photos of C.F. McIntyre exhibit, 1940s-1980s. (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - Including Powell Library, Middletown, Connecticut, Arizona, 1968-1970s. (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - Various photographs and reproductions, 1940s-1989. (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - Various photographs of family. Including photos of Powell Library dedication, 1920s-1960s. (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Baby pictures, 1980s-1993. (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - Various, 1987-1988. (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - Around the world trip aboard the S.S. President Harrison, 1925-1926. (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Europe especially Dijon, France. With M.F.K. Fisher, 1930s. (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - ** Family Photos
    - Various family photos not in an album, 1987-1989. (Box 241, Folder 3)
- Accession LSC-229-2015-03 backlog material, LSC-229-2015-03; 4 Audiovisual Carriers (4 audiocassettes) (Box 234)
- Accession LSC-2018-029 backlog material, LSC-2018-029